this the number one Forex Trading
strategy to avoid a losing streak let's
be honest we've all had losing streaks
like this one
[Music]
right
but on a serious note 87 percent of
Traders are not successful not 99 or 98
like I literally see the stats from
rocket they send me the stats and a
hundred percent of those 87 percent are
not successful because of psychology so
I'm going to be giving you guys my
number one trading strategy when it
comes to psychology make sure you guys
subscribe because we're almost at 100K
we got a big big giveaway coming out of
100K so hit that subscribe button I
don't know what side it is hit it oh oh
and by the way fill out the type form
below I want to know where you're at you
guys know I've done meet and greets all
around the world Columbia Peru Dr Puerto
Rico La Miami I'm doing New York right
now and I want to know where you guys
are based fill the type form below all
you have to do is put your name your
country and the state just so where I
know where you're at so whether the
majority of people are I pull up do a
meet and greet you get to meet me I'll
teach you for free and then I do
giveaways I give away challenges I'll
probably give away my watch can't give
away my hair lost my but fill out the
type form below I want to know where you
guys are at so I pull up so my number
one training trick before entering any
trade is why am I taking this trade why
is this worth one percent why is this
worth two percent and it simply comes
down to what are the odds of this trade
going in my favor versus not and when
you do this this puts you in a logical
mindset because if you take a trade and
you don't even know why you're taking it
you're simply already messing everything
down from the chain there so the first
thing that I do when I come to the
market is I ask myself why am I taking
this street is it really worth risking
this much of my account because if you
can't find the reasons if you can't
build a series of conferences on why
you're taking the trade you pretty much
just answer your own question there's no
reason why you should take it so before
you enter a trade ask yourself why am I
taking it is it a logical trade or am I
just being emotional
all right so I saw these clips of this
red G-Wagon just sending it through the
woods so we're gonna put it to the test
we put the car in trail mode so let's
see if it's true
thank you
oh
my gosh
all right so when I pulled up I thought
I lost the back tire and it was a tire
in the back but no this thing could
handle a beating like look at it it's
not even dirty bro like look there's
only thing that's dirty right here the
tires I mean I think like the rain
helped out a little bit but we were
hitting against the trees off camera we
hit a donut around it and everything but
these cars can handle a beating but that
leads me to my second point which is
going to be a human cannot take more
than three logical decisions a day
around money so why are you taking more
than two trades a day so my psychology
hack number two it is Cap yourself at
one to two trades a day risking one
percent because I see it all the time
when I do the account reviews on Rocket
people fail their challenges in three
four days like as soon as they get it
they fail it immediately obviously they
over risk and when I go look at the
amount of Trades they took they took 15
trades in three days like how is that
even possible how are you finding 15
trade setups in three four days it's
literally impossible you're just being
greedy emotional and wanting to be
active in the market so if you happy
yourself at one to two trades a day
you'll notice that higher probability
trades will come and you save your money
you save yourself for when those good
trades come because if you're already in
draw down eight percent when a good
opportunity comes you can't take it
because you either failure challenge or
you're too much into draw then and now
you're scared to take it so to avoid all
of those simple simple things all you
have to do is take one to two trades a
day max if you were to take my personal
personal advice one trade a day you
should not be taking two chain trades on
every single day because you just simply
cannot make more than three logical
decisions a day around money oh and by
the way this is uh the new Lambo wrap so
I actually got this to uh
match my garbage can see Park them next
to each other uh no but seriously this
is probably one of the most gangster
raps I've ever seen shout out to TBT
um so this is you know swing trading lab
we got our green color
um I think it looks far I don't know if
I like this site better the black side
better look look let's see the see the
green side
I'm gonna move my other car
or this side I was thinking for this
side to put the rims in Black because if
you notice the gold looks so weird and
if you notice look at the detail see the
green ball
that's called branding right there
that's called being creative
you guys get to learn
all right and that leads me to the next
to my next point which is greed there's
a lot of you greedy out there I
literally see it every single time I
review the accounts the same hour you
guys get your account credentials from
rocket you guys will literally take a
trade right away and that literally
shows me you're not taking any logical
trading decisions there's no way the
same hour you get your account this is a
good trade so agreed trick to
controlling yourself out there is let's
say you get your credentials on a
Wednesday or on a Thursday or on a
Friday do not trade the same day you get
your account because you're excited your
emotions are up you want to trade your
account you want to pass right don't do
it wait till a fresh new week so you
have a fresh new mindset when you're
going to start this challenge me
personally myself whenever I track any
account I do any challenge any account
flip anything I do I do it at the start
of a month at the start of the week
because if you start your account in the
middle of the month at the end of the
week how are you making 10 a month in
average you don't know because you're
starting right in the middle and then
the numbers are just completely off
every single time that is my tip one
when it comes to the greed and then my
second tip is for all of you ingredient
guys out there that you want to pass or
trade in one shot or you want to hold
your profits so you get a one to ten
risk to reward and you pass take a trade
let's say you're going to risk one
percent on the trade split that
percentage in half
so let's say you're going to take a 10
lot on a Euro USD buy take half a
percent on one trade half a percent on
the other they're the same exact trade
same entry same stop loss same take
profit so once your trade gets to your
original take profit close this trade
fully and then leave this one run
because you want to be greedy you want
to let it run so it keeps going and
making you more money let it run and
then over a period of 10 trades you're
gonna Realize by cutting your profits at
your original take profits which has to
be a minimum of a one to two point five
risk reward you're going to see how the
trade and your profitability is going to
make more sense how letting it run
trying to predict the top top of the
move before it comes back down it is
very difficult it is a lot easier to
just cut your losses short at one
percent and go home with your one to two
risk reward and you're going to be a
profitable Trader and you're greed
completely goes away so tip one make
sure you split the trade in half and
then stick to your rules with one the
other trade test out new things and then
when it comes to the first plan is do
not start your account at the middle of
the week wait to the beginning of the
week so you're not greedy
oh oh and by the way I'm a professional
poker player I don't know if you guys
knew I bet I bet this card I'm about to
bring out right now is uh like I don't
even know right so look this card right
here King of Hearts
well it's a heart but yeah so when it
comes to playing poker I get greedy
sometimes I say I'll buy in for whatever
a thousand or two thousand and I'm up
three four thousand I'm up three four
hundred percent of what I came in I'm
like no I want to beat everybody in the
table and that's not how this works
these guys that I play with they'll come
and buy them for 10K on a friendly game
and I'm like that's not a friendly game
at that point so take that all right so
this is me to my last point and it is
accountability you need to hold yourself
accountable when you break any of your
trading rules personally myself every
single time I break a trading rule I
hold myself accountable so if I break a
trading rule I can't eat a sweet I love
my sweets literally if I don't eat a
sweet after I eat I literally feel weird
so you need to hold yourself accountable
let's say your favorite thing to do is I
don't know eat french fries and you
break a rule from your trading plan or
any of these tips that I have given you
you cannot eat those french fries
because you broke your rules you don't
deserve to pay yourself something else
that I used to do as well and now I kind
of turned into liking which is cold
showers whenever I break cool I would
take a cold shower because when I'm in
there in that cold shower I'm like damn
I was breaking the wall worth being in
here like getting tortured but taking
Court showers now is like good for you
and all that stuff so holding yourself
accountable is one of the most important
things that we actually have Jordan here
um so Jordan he just you know he's been
consistent with YouTube and all that
stuff but he's been slacking so I'm
holding him accountable for everything
he's doing now but he has his little
checklist and everything that he does so
no no yo what's up bro it's good
so if you got I mean if you haven't seen
Jordan you gotta go see part one of the
last video If you haven't seen part two
it's because you haven't you know we
haven't posted it we're starting the
video right now so we got part two of
Guru versus student so he won the last
one and um this is like a sneak peek to
the video already you guys already saw
we shaved their heads
this part's gonna be interesting we
doubled the stakes so if you guys want
to make sure what happens and who wins
the actual ten thousand dollars this
time stay tuned to part two hit the
Subscribe button 100K coming let's go
two ten thousand was supposed to be
twenty thousand
yeah come on you said last time it was
double double or nothing